Summary

Mohammad has launched three start-ups (two mobile apps and one web app) from scratch to over 50,000 users and counting. Mohammad has also worked as a strategy and operations consultant, helping clients improve their operations, increase sales, satisfy regulatory requirements and cultivate innovation within their organization.

Professional Experiences

Co-Founder, CardStak Inc. SEP 2014 – PRESENT

 CardStak.com is used for networking events hosted by UC Berkeley Haas School of Business, School of Engineering, Law School and School of information. This platform has over 10,000 users and helped numerous students land job offers.

Skills: Entrepreneurship, Agile Product Management, Google Analytics, Amazon AWS

PricewaterhouseCoopers Management Consulting TORONTO, CANADA Senior Strategy Consultant, DEC 2012 - MAR 2014

- Executed global market scan regarding best practices in mortgage lending and developed recommendations for improving sales and customer experience. Presented analysis to executives and received approval for implementation
- Analyzed survey responses from approximately two thousand executives and developed the Canadian Edition for PwC
 Global Innovation study with insights on executive plans, mindsets and investments in innovation
- Helped a Credit Union achieve efficiencies through developing a model for customer segmentation, building standardized practices for business centers and other tactical improvements

Skills: Strategy, Leadership, Big Data Analytics, Presentation, Relationship Management

Bank of Montreal Financial Group Toronto, Canada

Operations Consultant, OCT 2011 - NOV 2012

- Delivered lean training and crafted training material as part of Operations Management Program for senior managers
- Developed a library of information on previous projects utilizing best practices, allowing consultants to leverage knowledge gained during previous projects for future projects
- Designed a training and selection process for new recruits within Product Operations resulting in 25% less error rates

Skills: Operations Management, Data Analysis, Presentation

Co-Founder, Smartiky Apps SEP 2009 – SEP 2011

- Launched two mobile apps and one web app with an aggregate user-base of over 50,000 users
 - o Smart Mail (http://tinyurl.com/og6wmbr). This app allows users to delete content of sent email messages, notifies users when email message has been read and creates beautiful templates for messages
 - o **Smart Poll** (http://tinyurl.com/pewkwmp). This was a mobile system for crowdsourcing opinions and was featured on numerous blogs and app review websites. This app used Facebook APIs

Skills: Agile Product Management, Full Stack Development, Android Java, SQL, Photoshop, Needs and usability assessment

Education

UC Berkeley (Berkeley, USA), Master of Information & Management Systems, 2014 – Present

- 1st place and audience award UC Berkeley Haas PLAY Hackathon (largest student-run tech conference in the Country)
- Graduate Student instructor for two courses: Principles of Business, Applied innovation at Haas School of Business

Sharif University of Technology (Tehran, Iran), B.Sc. Computer Engineering - Software, 2004 – 2008

Interests

- Excellent snowboarder and basketball player (won numerous inter-collegiate titles)
- Expert in creating designs with Adobe Photoshop over 9 years of experience